http://www.eni.gwdg.de/home/privacy-policy

Article 1 Information on the Collection of Personal Data
(1) In the following, we will provide information regarding the personal data that is collected when using our website. “Personal Data” is defined as any information which refers to you personally, such as name, address, email addresses or user behaviour.
(2) The entity responsible in the meaning of the General Data Protection Regulation and other national data protection acts as well as other data protection legislation is the:
European Neuroscience Institute Göttingen
-Institut der Universitätsmedizin Göttingen-
Grisebachstr. 5
37077 Göttingen
GERMANY
Tel.: +49 (0) 551 39-123 43/44
Fax: +49 (0) 551 39-123 43/46
E-Mail: [javascript protected email address]
Our Data Protection Officer:
Universitätsmedizin Göttingen
-Datenschutzbeauftragter-
37099 Göttingen
Telefon: +49 (0)551 39-22762
E-Mail: [javascript protected email address]
(3) When contacting us via email , we will use the personal data (your email address, in some cases your name and phone number as well) that you provide to us in order to answer your questions. We delete case-related data when storage is no longer necessary and restrict processing given statutory storage obligations.
(4) If we rely on contracted providers for individual functions of our services, we will inform you in detail about the particular processes below. In doing so, we will also mention the defined criteria pertaining to the storage period.
Article 2 Your Rights
(1) You have the following rights regarding our use of your personal data:
Right of access,
Right to correction or erasure,
Right to restriction of processing,
Right to object to the processing.
The right to data portability does not exist in the public-law sector. (Article 20 (2) sentence no. 2)
(2) You also have the right to lodge a complaint with a data protection supervisory authority about our processing of your personal data. If you wish to file a complaint, you may also contact the State Data Protection Authority for Lower Saxony, located at Prinzenstrasse 5, 30159 Hannover, Germany, phone number +49 (0)511/120-4500, [javascript protected email address].
Article 3 Collection of Personal Data when Using our Website
(1) When using the website for informational purposes only, i.e., if you do not register or otherwise provide us with information, we collect only that personal data which your browser transmits to our server. If you wish to view our website, we collect the following data to the extent that it is technically necessary for us in order to display our website to you as well as ensure its stability and security.
IP address
Date and time of request
Time zone difference to Greenwich Mean Time (GMT)
Content of request (specific page)
Access status/HTTP- status code
Data volume transmitted in each case
The website the request has come from Browser
Operating system and its interface
Language and browser software version.
(2) In addition to the aforesaid data, cookies are stored on your computer when you use our website. Cookies are small text files that are attributed to the browser you are using and stored on your hard drive and which provide specific information to the website that places the cookie (in this case, our website). Cookies cannot be used to run programmes or deliver viruses to your computer. Overall, they serve to make Internet content more user-friendly and effective.
(3) Use of cookies:
a) This website uses the following types of cookies, the extent and operating principle of which will be explained hereinafter:
Transient cookies (see b)
Persistent cookies (see c).
b) Transient cookies are automatically deleted when you close your browser. In particular, these include session cookies. These store a session ID, which is used to assign various requests from your browser to a common session. This allows your computer to be recognised when you return to our website. The session cookies are removed once you log out or close your browser.
c) Persistent cookies are automatically deleted after a specified period, which may vary depending on the cookie. You can delete cookies at any time in the security settings of your browser.
d) You can configure your browser settings according to your wishes and, for example, refuse to accept third-party cookies or all cookies. Please be aware that you may not be able to use all features of this website if you refuse to accept cookies.
e) Given that you have a user account, we use cookies to identify you on subsequent visits. Otherwise, you would have to enter your login information every time you visit our website.
f) The Flash cookies used are not recorded by your browser, but by your Flash plug-in. We also use HTML5 storage objects that are stored on your device. These objects store the required data regardless of the browser you are using, and they do not have an automatic expiry date. If you do not wish the Flash cookies to be processed, you must install an appropriate add-on, e.g. "Clear Flash Cookies" for Mozilla Firefox (https://addons.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/addon/clear-flash-cookies/) or use Google Chrome, which supports the deletion of flash cookies. You can prevent the use of HTML5 storage objects by using “Private Mode”, which is available in all modern browsers. In addition, we recommend that you regularly delete your cookies and browser history manually.
(4) Matomo
This website uses Matomo for web analytics. For this purpose, usage information generated by "cookies" (including your shortened IP address) is transmitted to the server and stored for usage analysis purposes after it has been made anonymous. The information generated by the cookie(s) about your usage of the site will not be transmitted to third parties. You can prevent the use of cookies by configuring your browser software accordingly; however, please be aware that if you do this, you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.
Partners and Sponsors
University Medical Center Göttingen
Max Planck Society
Home
About the Institute
Press Releases
Board of Directors
Advisory Board
